Veronica Eulenberg

Page 1

<u>650-224-0951</u> • <u>veronica.eulenberg@gmail.com</u> • Dallas, TX <u>veronicodes.com</u>

Front End React Engineer

I have 7 years of work experience in software development. I thrive where I am able to troubleshoot and collaborate on customer solutions. I love to fix and customize user-focused, responsive-design and cross-browser compatible solutions. My strengths are in CSS, JavaScript, Node, React, and SQL. Seeking to work with professionals that have a positive attitude and a good sense of humor.

Skills

React/Redux • JavaScript • Node • HTML/CSS/Bootstrap • UI/UX • GIT • SQL • API

Professional Experience

Software Engineer • Freelance • Remote • 3/2021 - Present

- Taught HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Native, Node, PHP and Scratch to students 1-on-1, ages 6 36.
- Crafted 5+ apps to fit customer requirements using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Hugo, Bulma, and Bootstrap.
- Led meetings over Zoom, Google Hangouts, Microsoft's Skype, and in-person.
- Collaborated on UI/UX design in cross-functional teams.
- Ported apps between platforms: Google Chrome plugin -> website, WordPress -> Hugo.

Data Annotator • Moveworks • Remote • 8/2021 - 4/2023

- Developed JavaScript programs (bookmarklets) to make annotation faster.
- Manipulated data in Google Sheets with formulas and functions.
- Categorized, tagged, labeled, and evaluated 60+ user queries an hour.

Front End React Engineer • LifeOmic • Remote • 3/2021 - 6/2021

- Built a customer support app with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Material UI, React, Axios, Apollo, GraphQL, REST API.
- Answered 40+ technical tickets a day to solve customer issues.
- Contributed to app design 10+ times at weekly UI/UX (User Experience) meetings.

Front End React Engineer • MX Technologies • Remote • 5/2020 - 9/2020

- Fixed 50+ bugs with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Native, Redux.
- Took part in leading developer meetings.
- Maintained documentation with JIRA, Confluence, and GitHub.
- Prepared 5+ designs for complex bug fix meetings with other developers.
- Tested with Firefox, Chrome, Safari, Internet Explorer 11 with VirtualBox, and mobile.

Continued On Next Page...

Veronica Eulenberg

Page 2

<u>650-224-0951</u> • <u>veronica.eulenberg@gmail.com</u> • Dallas, TX <u>veronicodes.com</u>

Professional Experience (Continued)

Full Stack React Engineer • JustUtahCoders • Salt Lake City, Utah • 9/2019 - 9/2020

- Modified 2 existing apps with a 10-person team using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, RegEx, Node, and SQL.
- Collaborated with a cross-functional team on structure of PDF parser results.
- Built developer tool for junior developers to see PDF parsing results 50% faster.
- Added UI for complex SQL queries that aggregated user data from forms.

Full Stack WordPress Engineer • J.F. Web Development • Remote • 2/2017 - 1/2021

- Modified 10+ websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL and jQuery to comply with requests.
- Developed 5+ WordPress/WooCommerce sites with Beaver Builder page builder and CSS.
- Used WordPress hooks, plugins, PHP, and JavaScript to enhance User Experience.
- Wrote 10+ detailed progress reports on new feature implementation.
- Transferred 20+ domain names between HostGator, BlueHost, 1&1, and GoDaddy.

Personal Projects

Project Ticket Manager

- Built back end API in Node using Express, Passport, Mongoose, and MongoDB.
- Modified React + Tailwind front end app to ingest my CRUD and Auth APIs.
- Developed login and ticket editing and assignment functionality.

Video Subtitle Editor

- Developed an app to edit subtitles using JavaScript, VideoJS, and Bootstrap.
- Built functionality to replay sections of video using timestamps until audio is heard.
- Created a simple UI to easily create, update, delete, upload, and download subtitles.
- Forged a dashboard to work on multiple subtitle files at the same time with ease.

Education

Self-Directed Software Development Training • 9/2016 - Present

Coursework from Udemy, FreeCodeCamp, W3Schools, edX, Coursera, Lynda, etc.

Security+ Certificate • 11/2021 - 11/2024

General and Software Security Training

Portnov Computer School • 12/2017 - 03/2018

Software Quality Assurance Training